This is Saho Tanaka from Crown Pup.
And I am Kaon of Kyushu Jyoshiryoku.
Nice to meet you.
Yay!
So, this is a little bit of a Tidl dialogue project,
It's almost the first time for us to meet, isn't it?
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a little nervous.
But it seems we have a lot in common.
For example, we are the same age. We are 20 years old now, right?
We are in the class of 2002.
You are a Goat sign, right?
I am a January.
I am in December.
We are very close.
We are the same, aren't we? Cell sign.
And my blood type is A.
What is your height?
I am 155cm.
That's right, I'm 149cm.
But we are the smallest in the group.
The smallest.
I'm like the smallest in the group.
That's amazing. Just by looking at them now.
We have a lot in common.
Thank you very much.
When I squeeze her, she tends to be crushed,
Yes, that's right. I sometimes get buried in them.
Yes, that's true.
What is the height difference between the other members?
There are some members who are about 160cm tall,
I see.
They are all relatively tall.
Yes, they are.
The way they look at you.
Like that. It's like that. Everyone else is high, too. Yes, they are. The line of sight. It's like that.
Is it like that?
The others are very expensive, too,
Yes.
I can totally understand.
Also, I just overheard that you used to play the violin,
I also overheard that you used to play the violin.
Yes, I did. Yes, I did.
I used to play when I was little,
Is that right?
Yes, I did.
That's great.
I can't play at all now.
I can't play at all. That part is also the same. Wow, that's great. I can't play at all. I can't play at all.
We are the same there, too.
That's amazing.
I see.
I'm sure there are many, many more if you dig them up.
I'm glad.
Q. What kind of person is Kanon?
Sahorn-chan?
Yes, that's right. People call me Sahorn.
I am usually called Kanon or Kanon,
But I am sometimes called Nontan,
So, I'll be Nontan.
Yes, I am.
Okay, Nontan.
Sahorn.
Oh, good.
Thank you.
Cute. Nontan and Sahorn.
Nontan.
It's kind of fluffy, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Amazing.
It's amazing. I don't know what to do.
Nice to meet you.
You're an amazing people person.
I'm a people person too.
That's amazing.
I wonder what it is.
I have an image of Kyushu Jyoshiryoku as a really cool person,
Their outfits are red.
I have an image of them looking cool,I had the image of being "puckish",
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you that much about him,
I have an image of you as a very good-looking person,
I had an image of Blancpop as an older sister,
But when I saw the live video,
I was surprised at how cute the songs were,
Takenaka's song "Yokki" was cute,
Thank you very much.
That changed my impression of her as a cute adult.
You are all really good singers.
You are the one who should be thanking me.
Do you have an image of red in your costumes?
Red is the color of the costumes nowadays, isn't it?
Like the costumes?
Yes, I am. I'm glad.
And the crown here. It's always on, isn't it? It's cute. It makes me happy. Also, the climax crown here is always on, isn't it?
It makes me happy.
Isn't the climax so cute?
Really?
Yes, it is. It's a little sparkly,
It's cute.
Q. What kind of member are you?
I am a very spoiled little sister.
Most of the other members are older than you,
I am the youngest. I am the youngest,
I see.
What am I in charge of?
I'm in charge of eating.
Is that right?
There are times when they prepare lunch boxes or other food for live concerts,
I'm in charge of going to see them first thing and telling them that it was just for today.
That's nice. I see.
When I went there today, it was fried.
It was fried.
That's nice. Sounds fun.
I like to eat too,
Really?
I want to eat with you.
Let's go out to eat.
What do you like?
I like beef tongue, chocolate mint, peaches, and mangoes,
I've never had chocolate mint.
Is that so?
It's like you don't like to eat?
Yes, that's right. Choco mint has two choices, right?
Like toothpaste and super tasty teeth.
I had heard that, so I never got around to trying it.
Do you have any recommendations for chocolate mint?
But I'm still a Super Cup chocolate mint guy.
Both in quantity?
I see.
If you're of the two-sided mindset, I'd recommend the Super Cup Choco Mint.
There is certainly a lot of it. That's right.
If you want to eat something tasty, there is something called Choco Mint.
Ice cream?
Yes.
Boomin' drink.
You may have had it before.
What does it taste like?
Quality.
If you are looking for quality.
I see. Then try some.
I have double skin.
Taste the water.
I'll stop by on my way home and take a look.
You're here for the Masked Girls' Masked Girls Expedition, aren't you? All the time.
That's right.
I come every month, but I drive there,
By car?
That's right. I drive from Fukuoka to Tokyo every month,
I want to be comfortable in the car,
So I wear loose-fitting clothes that are easy to move around in. I wear loose-fitting clothes.
How long does it take?
About 13 hours.
That's a lot of work.
Because you're sitting for most of the time.
What? !
Legs and all.Or legs?
Do you also have shoulders?
Yes, I do.
Wow.
That's right,
That's right.
I don't do it unless I'm relaxed.
With a pillow or something like this,
But I'm talking about the view of Mt.
a It's from the inside, so, yes, it's true.
I'm not very good at making things that I bring along with me.
Rats.
I'm the type of person who doesn't make things last minute.
I've got a big one, so I pack it rather tightly.
I'm of the school that doesn't do anything until the last minute.
So I only bring the minimum.
I don't like the idea of having to get things locally if something happens.
I really only carry clothes and makeup.
There was one time when I had a very large baggage.
I took a gold leaf roller with me once when I was doing several boxes.
I was on a huge buying spree.
I was cheating on my wife.
Isn't it pretty big?
It's so big.
I had a big carry-on.
I took it with me once, but I didn't need it.
I took it once, but I didn't need it.
I really didn't use it. I just rolled it around once and that was it.
You want to take something new with you, don't you?
I brought my iron and other things for nothing.
Or skin care?
That's right.
I bought this, so I'm going to take it with me.
After all, it might have been good before I knew it.
You are a worrier, aren't you? That's amazing.
I understand.
You do things at the very last minute, but because you are a worrier, you always cram in a lot of things at the last minute.
Then, at the last minute, you decide to do this too.
That's right. Yes, I do.
It's true that they don't bring snacks or miso soup, even though they're in Japan.
I often see such things overseas, but not at all. I feel relieved to bring them even though they are in Japan. But with miso for the soup stock, you know. Do you think miso tastes different in Kyushu?
I wonder. Is it the same?
Is it the same?
You don't cook, do you?
Miso?
What is it?
But I don't think it's red.
Is it the same?
What about white?
What is red?
I heard it's something from Nagoya,
Is it a dark one? I don't think it's dark. White? What is red? I don't know,
It's the dark kind, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
I don't think they have dark cups.
Then I guess it's the same.
Barley.
I don't know that much about it,
It tastes like ryotei.
It's amazing.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it? Miso soup.
I love it.
If you were to add an ingredient to miso soup, what would be your favorite?
Hmmm...
Wow. I'm sure it's here. From when you spread it out.
Q. What was it like?
I don't know,
It was amazing.
It was kind of a crazy story,
But it was the first half.
We had a lot in common. I'm sure there are many more if we look for them.
So, let's find more before the next night land.
I want to talk a lot.
Thank you very much.